4icu.org 2017-06-18

# Privacy Statement

**Information about our Organisation and Web site**

We are based in Australia.  
Our principal activity is: Directory of World Universities and Colleges; [learn more](http://www.4icu.org/about/).  
Our privacy policy covers uniRank.org and its website: 

| **Organisation Name:** | uniRankâ„¢  
---|---  
**Address:** | 2C/5 Tambua Street   
**City, Zip:** | Sydney, 2009   
**State:** | NSW   
**Country:** | Australia   
**Controller:** | Fabio Fatuzzo   
**Website(s):** | http://www.4icu.org  
  
**Providing Visitors with Anonymous Access**

You can access our website home page and browse our site without disclosing your personal data.

**The services and links of our Web site**

Our website does not enable our visitors to communicate with other visitors or to post information to be accessed by others. 

**Third party websites and Cookie Policy**

Our website does include links to third party web service providers including **Google AdSense** , **Google Analytics** and other advertising or social media platforms which may use cookies to personalise content and ads, to provide social media features and to analyse our traffic. We also share non personal information about your use of our site with our social media, advertising and analytics partners who may combine it with other information youâ€™ve provided to them or theyâ€™ve collected from your use of their services. To learn more please check [how Google uses data when you use our partners' sites or apps](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/partners/).

**Automatic Collection of Information**

We do not automatically log personal data nor do we link information automatically logged by other means with personal data about specific individuals. 

We do not use cookies to store personal data nor do we link non-personal information stored in cookies with personal data about specific individuals. 

**Data Collection and Purpose Specification**

We collect the personal data that you may volunteer while using our services and filling our forms. 

We do not collect information about our visitors from other sources, such as public records or bodies, or private organisations. 

To access the table of personal data collected and purposes for which they are used, please  click here 

We do not collect or use personal data for any purpose other than that indicated in the table below. 

If we wish to use your personal data for a new purpose, we offer you the means to consent to this new purpose: privacy @ 4icu . org

**Children's Privacy**

We do not knowingly collect personal data from children.

**Disclosure and Visitor Choice**

We do not disclose your personal data to our subsidiaries or other organisations.

**Confidentiality / Security**

We do not give visitors to our Web site the option of using a secure transmission method to send us their personal data. 

We have implemented security policies, rules and technical measures to protect the personal data that we have under our control from: 

  * unauthorised access 

  * improper use or disclosure

  * unauthorised modification

  * unlawful destruction or accidental loss

We ensure that your personal data will not be disclosed to State institutions and authorities except if required by law or other regulation.

**Access to the personal data we may hold about you**

You can ask us, by: 

  * sending an email (privacy @ 4icu . org) 

whether we are keeping personal data about you.

Upon request, which you can indicate by: 

  * sending an email (privacy @ 4icu . org) 

We will provide you with a readable copy of the personal data which we keep about you, within a month. - although we may before require proof of your identity -. We will provide the information without any charge. 

We allow you to challenge the data that we hold about you and, where appropriate, you may have the data: 

  * erased

  * rectified or amended

  * completed

We reserve the right to refuse to provide our visitors with a copy of their personal data, but will give reasons for our refusal.

We do, however, allow you to challenge our decision to refuse to provide you with a copy of your personal data.

**Privacy Compliance**

Our privacy policy is compliant with the following instrument: Australian Privacy Act - www.privacy.gov.au 

There are no global or regional regulatory or self-regulatory schemes applicable to our web site or organisation. 

In order to demonstrate that our privacy policy accords with the above privacy instrument, we are: 

  * voluntarily committed to a Self Assessment procedure 

**Self Assessment procedure**

**Privacy Policy Person** | Fabio Fatuzzo   
---|---  
**URL** | www.4icu.org  
**Country** | Australia   
  
**Primary personal data/Business information**

**x** | volunteered by each visitor   
---|---  
\-  | collected from public records or bodies   
\-  | collected from private organisations   
  
**Primary personal data** |  Technical administration of the Web site  |  Research &development  |  Customer Administration  |  Marketing  |  Trading in personal data   
---|---|---|---|---|---  
Name  | **x** |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-   
Gender  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-   
Address  | **x** |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-   
E-mail address  | **x** |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-   
Phone/Fax number  | **x** |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-   
other (describe) |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-   
**Business Information** |  Technical administration of the Web site  |  Research & development  |  Customer Administration  |  Marketing  |  Trading in personal data   
---|---|---|---|---|---  
Employer/organisation  | **x** |  \-  |  \-  | **x** |  \-   
Job title  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-   
Address  | **x** |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-   
E-mail address  | **x** |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-   
Phone/Fax number  | **x** |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-   
other (describe)   
_Website information_ | **x** | **x** |  \-  | **x** |  \-   
  
**Other personal details and profiling data**

\-  | volunteered by each visitor   
---|---  
\-  | collected from public records or bodies   
\-  | collected from private organisations   
  
|  Technical administration of the Web site  |  Research & development  |  Customer Administration  |  Marketing  |  Trading in personal data   
---|---|---|---|---|---  
Personal details  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-   
Physical description  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-   
Family characteristics  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-   
Education and skills  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-   
Life style or personal tastes  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-   
Financial resources  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-   
other (describe) |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-   
  
**Identifiers**

\-  | volunteered by each visitor   
---|---  
\-  | collected from public records or bodies   
\-  | collected from private organisations   
  
|  Technical administration of the Web site  |  Research & development  |  Customer Administration  |  Marketing  |  Trading in personal data   
---|---|---|---|---|---  
On-line identifiers  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-   
Financial identifiers  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-   
identifiers assigned by Public bodies  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-   
Biometrics identifiers  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-   
other (describe)  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-   
  
**Specific Data**

\-  | volunteered by each visitor   
---|---  
\-  | collected from public records or bodies   
\-  | collected from private organisations   
  
|  Technical administration of the Web site  |  Research & development  |  Customer Administration  |  Marketing  |  Trading in personal data   
---|---|---|---|---|---  
Racial or ethnic origin  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-   
Political opinions  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-   
Religious or philosophical beliefs  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-   
Trade union membership  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-   
Health/Medical data  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-   
Sex life  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-   
Police/Justice data such as civil/criminal actions brought by or against the visitor  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-   
other (describe)  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-   
  
**Your acceptance of these terms**

By using this website, you signify your acceptance of this Privacy and Cookie Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our website. Your continued use of the website following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

**Changes to this privacy policy**

uniRankâ„¢ has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect your privacy. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.
